extremecfnm.com 2005-12-31

# About CFNM Affiliation Program

Latest News...

 **Members Message Board** \- 1st November 2005: With our commitment to improving the services we offer, we are proud to announce the launch of our members message board.

This will allow like-minded people that have joined our sites to chat freely with each other and take part in a true CFNM community.

 **AdultXfun.com 2257 Statement** \- 22nd June 2005: AdultXfun.com 2257 Statement. We recommend our US Affiliates read this statment  
AdultXfun.com is a European company and as such is bound by EU laws. The European community has developed a directive that was passed by the Council of Ministers in October 1995 and came into force in October 1998, obliging all member states to block the flow of personal data to states without adequate protection, subject to the derogations listed in Article 26. America maintained that self-regulation was a preferred approach to dealing with privacy issues. America is not in line with the European community on this subject. However all webmasters, as we are, should be bound by the laws that are in affect in whatever country you reside in, i.e. promo material used on websites must be compliant with your local laws. AdultXfun.com is bound by the EU law which is we are not allowed to issue personal information without adequate protection of that information. The new 2257 regulations do not allow us to comply without breaking EU laws. We will be seeking further clarification of our position with our legal council including the possibility of filing a TRO on behalf of our AdultXfun.com members. We are working on a number of ideas to assist our American friends, members and affiliates. Questions regarding this topic can be directed to affiliates@adultxfun.com

 **New Hosted Pages** \- 19th January 2005: AdultXFun now features a dedicated section of hosted pages. Why waste time offline designing your own pages, when you can pick and choose from our ever-growing selection. Each page has a distinctive look and feel and  
captures the attention with great graphics and the key phrases that make us stand out from the crowd. [CLICK HERE](http://www.adultxfun.com/index.php/hosted)

|    | 

About Us

AdultXFun is a well established adult entertainment company, with our main business running adult websites. We pride ourselves on creating and offering some of the highest quality adult content on the Internet, you will not find our own content anywhere else, this is unique to us.

We have invested a lot of time and money over the years to produce some of the most pleasing designs, we also run and maintain our own servers to make sure that everything runs snoothly, just as it should. By running our own hardware it eliminates a lot of problems that other adult companies may have to put up with.

All of our sites are running 24 hours a day and 7 days a week, to guarantee this we have techincal staff continually monitoring the performance of our servers and sites. We are proud to say that we are a 24/7 company and hope you will agree with out statements when you visit one of our sites.

Privacy Policy Statement

For casual visitors to our website, we do **not** collect any information regarding domains, e-mail addresses, or any other personal details.

The information that we collect from our customers is **not** shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending an email to us via the contact page stating that you do not wish to receive any further communications from our company.

If you have supplied us with your postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products, services or upcoming events. Please provide us with your exact name and address if you do not wish to receive such mailings, send details via the contact page.

Persons who have supplied us with their telephone number online may receive calls from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. Please provide us with your correct phone number via the contact page if you do not wish to receive any such contact.

#### Our Privacy Statement

Antarctic Dot Com Ltd. - and all associated websites - have created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our customers. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our websites.

We use cookies to help maintain a consistent experience for our customers. Cookies are only used in a few sections of our site, specifically the online shop, this enables us to keep track of the products in your shopping cart. At no time is any personal information stored within a cookie.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and keep track of how many visitors our websites have had. At no time is your IP address used to help identify you.

This site contains links to other sites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

Our websites use an orderform for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitors' contact information such as email address and financial information (i.e. account or credit card numbers). Contact information from orderforms are used to send order details and information to our company from our customers only. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill customers for products and/or services. The information that you provide to us will not be shared or sold to any other company or individuals at any time.

#### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or newsgroups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. When you make a purchase "add to shopping cart" you will be taken to a secure server. At the bottom of the page you will see a small padlock that informs you that your information is encrypted and you are on a secure server (SSL). Also, in the address bar the URL should start with "https://". This site only uses the highest level of Internet Security. At no time will your information be in any danger of theft.

#### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

If you do not wish to be placed on our mailing list please contact us via our contact page with a request to be removed. This will be carried out without any hesitation.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If at any time you wish to contact us, please go to the contact page. Here you will be able to contact us via on-line form, telephone, or mailing address.

Warranty / Returns Policy

We want you to feel confident when shopping with us. That is why our returns policy is very simple and straightforward.

We want you to be satisfied with your purchase, if for whatever reason you are not you may return the product to us in its original condition. Any unopened CD, DVD or VHS tape in its original condition returned within 10 days of receipt of your order will receive a full refund.

If any open video or audio product is defective, it must be returned to us within 30 day to be replaced by another audio or video of the same program.

No authorization is required. Simply indicate the reason for your return, include the packing slip, and box the package securely. If you do not have your packing slip, please indicate your name, address and the order number on a separate piece of paper, and send the package to the address on the contact page.

We cannot accept responsibility for lost items during transit, we recommend that you ship by USPS Insured Post or any other service, like UPS or FedEx, which offers tracking numbers.

**Items Received as a Gift**

If a product received from us was sent to you as a gift, we can issue a cheque refund to the gift recipient at the same address to which the order was shipped. Please include your packing slip or the name of the person who gave the gift.

Please include your e-mail address so that we may confirm your refund.

**Refunds**

We will notify you via e-mail of your refund once we have received the returned items. Please note that we can refund shipping costs only if the return is a result of our error.

**Need more information or assistance?**

If you have any problems with your order, please don't hesitate to contact us.   
  
---|---|---
